(A Shining Day)
Let me bring in the star of this week's Rainbow Live.
When the preview was released, it went viral.
- Really? - Yes, it was crazy.
She's attracting attention as a scene stealer...
in every project she acts in.
I present Choi Ji Su to you.
- Welcome to the show. - Welcome.
(Welcome to the show.)
- Oh, my. - My gosh.
- Hello. - Hi.
Apple.
(An adorable actress stealing the spotlight from the get-go)
(Her refreshing charm like an apple went viral.)
(She perfectly pulled off playing a lovely character...)
(with her attention to detail.)
("Actress Choi Ji Su's Nomination Proves She's the Next Big Rookie")
(She was even nominated for the Best Rookie Award.)
(Actress Choi Ji Su)
Hello. I'm Actress Choi Ji Su.
All right.
I watched her drama, "Undercover Miss Hong."
- Right. - Yes.
- When I watched it... - "Apple."
- Right. "Apple." - "Apple."
You played Kang No Ra.
This is your first time joining the Rainbow Club.
Tell us how you feel to be here.
Walking from the door to this spot felt like forever.
- Really? - Yes.
So I'm really nervous.
- Right. - I see.
Yes.
- Relax and be yourself. - Relax.
- You should relax. - Try to relax.
When you were watching our show,
was there a memorable episode?
I remember your episode about the dry-style bathroom.
- My house? - Yes.
- The dry-style bathroom. - Bathrooms are important to me too.
- I watched the preview. - Really?
- You did? - You guys are quite similar.
- It felt great to watch it. - I clean the toilet bowl...
right after I use it.
- Some people do the same thing. - Right.
- I see. - I do it too.
Let's dive into the day-to-day life of Choi Ji Su.
(Sunny Index: 100)
(The sun is beaming into the room.)
(She's still asleep without moving an inch.)
You haven't seen your room on the screen before.
Right.
(You haven't seen your room on the screen before.)
(The melodious morning alarm goes off.)
(Grabbing)
(She quickly turns off the alarm.)
(Opening her eyes)
Oh, my.
Hello. I've been living alone for three years.
I'm Actress Choi Ji Su.
My gosh. She's adorable.
- Welcome. - Oh, my.
(She gets up as soon as she opens her eyes.)
(She's still half asleep.)
(Staring)
Gamja.
(Gamja!)
- She's my daughter. - Her name is Gamja.
- How cute. - She looks so beautiful.
Wait. Hey.
- She can fill the whole bowl. - The bowl is full.
(After a morning greeting to Gamja...)
(Grabbing)
(Rolling)
I have a cat in the house.
- I have to do that no matter what. - You have to do it.
- Because of the fur. - Really?
That's necessary.
(Cleaning meticulously as soon as she gets up)
(Pulling up)
(Great. It's clean now.)
I love how clean her room is.
I live in Goyang, Gyeonggi Province.
The view from my house is great.
- It's perfect for one person. - It's beautiful.
And it's a small place.
But it comes with a lot of cabinets which are useful.
It's a cozy little house.
(A kitchen shelf)
(A hanging soap, a drying dish mat)
- You can dry the dishes there. - She's so neat.
You're using every corner of the house very efficiently.
(She efficiently filled up the cabinets as well.)
- Her cleaning skills are top-tier. - Seriously.
(Inside her well-organized fridge...)
- She labeled them with dates. - Gosh, this is great.
Otherwise, I forget.
(Baeksang Arts Awards)
You went to the Baeksang Arts Awards.
Yes.
- You were invited. - I was.
- He's acting so arrogant. - I see.
My gosh, Baeksang Arts Awards...
- Only superstars are invited. - That's right.
(That's right.)
- He's so arrogant. - My goodness.
I was never invited.
(She goes to the door after making the bed.)
(Rustling)
- The cat litter box. - I see. It's her routine.
- I have to dig it up. - You must dig up the potatoes.
She pooped a lot.
(She cleans the litter box like a pro.)
(Rushing)
Gamja.
(What?)
Snack?
- Look at you coming down. - She can understand that?
Yes, she could understand the word since she was little.
(She charges down at the mention of snacks.)
Let's go.
(For Gamja who has rushed down,)
(she brings out the treat right away.)
It's good, isn't it?
(Look at my daughter eating it with gusto.)
(While Gamja is enjoying her snack...)
(Let me quickly wash up.)
(Grabbing the toothbrush)
(Well, I'm almost out of toothpaste.)
(Squeezing up every bit of the toothpaste)
You're using it up.
- Right. - Otherwise, it'd be wasteful.
- The walls are shiny. I love it. - Yes.
Oh, you noticed it.
The fluorescent light has to be reflected off it.
- Right. - That defines a clean house.
Shouldn't there be bugs inside the fluorescent lights?
Kian84, I'm curious about the fluorescent light in your house.
My house? My house is clean.
Because he moves when it's starting to get dirty.
(He moves instead of cleaning the house.)
(After brushing her teeth...)
(Putting it on)
- Oh, no! - She's so clean.
- Why? - Oh, no!
- Why? You look cute. - You look cute.
You look fine.
(She washes her face with a cute spa headband.)
(Dabbing)
She has porcelain skin...
unlike us with a yellowish skin tone.
(Opening)
(She takes something out from the cabinet.)
- Yes! You need a storage box. - That's...
- I have one too. - my treasure box.
(She starts off her day with a cleaning session.)
(She pushes up her sleeves...)
(and goes into the bathroom.)
(It's the toothpaste she used up earlier.)
- The used-up toothpaste? - Yes. That's quite useful.
- Yes. - There's a lot left inside.
(She takes off the headband.)
(Grabbing a pair of scissors)
(Cutting the toothpaste tube)
I can tell she's done this before by the way she cuts it.
- She's not hesitant. - Right.
Okay.
(In no time, she cuts open the tube.)
- What? What are you doing? - What?
What's she doing?
I usually spread out my cleaning tasks...
throughout the week.
(Monday: Shake out the blankets, Tuesday: Clean the shelves...)
- My goodness. - My gosh.
Oh, my.
- My gosh. - What's that? I should buy it too.
- What's that? I want to buy it. - That's...
really useful.
You can check the progress when you put it on the door.
- You keep seeing it. - Yes.
What do I need to type in to find that?
- Is it a to-do list board? - Yes, that's it.
A to-do list board?
I wasn't supposed to clean the washer,
but I used up the toothpaste.
So I'm going to clean the washer too.
The shine lasts longer...
- with toothpaste. - That's right.
I always run the washer...
with the toothpaste once I'm done with it.
(Grabbing)
(She grabs an empty water bottle and sits on the floor.)
(Covering the floor)
(She's placing the empty bottle in front of the drainage hole.)
(She grabs the drainage hose with one hand.)
- Right. - What's she doing?
(Inserting a stick)
You're draining the water.
- If I don't do that, - Right.
- I'd be washing my clothes in mold. - That's right.
(A cleaning task to remove mold from the water)
If you try that at home, you'll see a lot of dirt and mold.
(Removing)
(She disassembles the detergent box.)
(Getting ready)
(She even puts on the latex gloves.)
(Coating the rubber seal with detergent)
(She grabs a toothbrush right away.)
(Scrubbing)
- It's so moldy inside the seal. - Right.
- Just check it just once. - Right.
- It smells awful. - That's true.
- Great. - Really?
She's that thorough?
Where do you get this kind of information?
- Wait. - That was random.
- "Where do you get it?" - "Where do you get it?"
My mom gave me some tips.
Because I only look up cleaning products,
- Right. - I only see videos...
- about cleaning tips on my feed. - Right.
- Your feed is all about cleaning. - Yes.
I bet her feed and my feed are about the same.
I watch a lot of videos from cleaning crews...
- Right? - on YouTube.
- Does that make you feel good? - Yes.
(Excited)
- There's a famous guy for it. - Just now, she...
- Yes. - She just hit a fourth-octave note.
- There's a famous guy, right? - They're my teachers.
(Scrubbing hard)
(This should do it for the inside.)
(Next, she disassembles the drainage hole.)
- That's where the dirt comes out. - Right.
(She covers it with an alcohol wet wipe.)
With a wet wipe?
- The hole. - Is that necessary?
Gosh, she's so clean.
(She finishes cleaning the bottom of the washer in a flash.)
(The disassembled parts of the washer...)
- Right. - Yes.
No way.
(She washes them separately.)
- With an old toothbrush? - Yes.
She stores all the old toothbrushes...
- Of course. - and uses them.
- Gosh, that's amazing. - She's so thorough.
(Okay. I'm done with this too.)
Nice.
(She reassembles them right after cleaning them.)
Great.
I'm done.
- You just run it with toothpaste. - Right.
(Once she runs the washer with the used toothpaste tube,)
(she's done cleaning the washer.)
I have a separate box for recyclables.
My place is small, so I don't have a place for recyclables.
She's using the space very efficiently.
(Oh, I almost forgot.)
(Rustling)
(This time, she puts on a mask.)
(Ji Su grabs her phone...)
(and goes into the bathroom.)
- What? - My goodness.
- It's my work song. - Yes.
I put on baseball games.
That's great.
You clean the ceiling?
- It's really dusty up there. - Nice.
I've never seen anyone clean the ceiling.
- It's really dusty up there. - Right.
- It's the worst. - Cat fur goes up...
- to the ceiling too. - Right.
No way.
(Diligently wiping the ceiling)
I've been on this show for a decade.
It's my first time seeing anyone clean the ceiling.
That's crazy.
(Wiping the entire ceiling)
You can tell what someone is like...
- just by looking at their bathroom. - Right!
When you go over to someone's house, you can learn a lot...
about their routine by looking at their bathroom.
Like their daily routine.
That's why I think...
- bathrooms should always be clean. - I agree.
So you're judging people by their bathroom?
So it's...
That's your inferiority complex talking.
(Joking)
(She puts down the mop she used to wipe the ceiling.)
(Grabbing the next tool)
- What's that? - What?
- What? - I can't reach all the way up.
That's a great product for short women like me.
Once you spray it on the wall...
- Does it get soaked? - It turns white.
That's when you can wash it off.
- It's like washing a car. - Yes.
You can buy the same cleaning products I have.
- I'm really going to buy them. - I see.
- That's cost-efficient. - I only buy reasonably-priced ones.
(Moved)
(Spraying)
My goodness.
(Spraying over the entire wall)
(There's no hesitation in her movement.)
(Like an artist working on a masterpiece,)
(her movements are bold and confident.)
- My gosh. This is really necessary. - It is.
(Spraying)
Gosh, that's crazy.
I use cleaning products...
with skin-safe ingredients...
to thoroughly clean the walls and the floor.
(Showering the entire bathroom)
(I'm done with the walls.)
(A generous dollop of toothpaste)
That's right. You should clean that.
She cleans that too?
- That's crazy. - This is great.
(She quickly cleans the bottom of the sink.)
- She works really fast. - This is crazy.
(She scrubs the shower rail next.)
My gosh. She's going above and beyond.
There you go.
Watching her clean is so satisfying.
I really hate it...
- when the shower rail gets rusty. - That's the worst.
I use those toothbrushes with thin bristles to clean that.
Just buy one and try cleaning it with the toothbrush.
- That's it. - The gaps on the shower hose?
- The hose is really dirty. - What?
A lot of stains come off it.
- So I clean the hose. - That's it.
(Scrubbing hard with the toothbrush)
Let me give you a tip.
There's a brush with bristles on the back like toothbrushes.
- You can use that and turn it. - That will be much better.
That's much better for that.
- Do you want a better tip? - I'm learning today.
There's a shower hose without the gaps.
(The cleaning seniors excitedly share cleaning tips.)
I'm learning so much today.
- You should form a cleaning trio. - Right.
- We should form a trio. - You guys can form one.
- Sung Hwan too. - The three of you should do it.
We can be the Cleanies.
(They'd go by Cleanies.)
- Great. - I love it.
We should form a cleaning club.
(The youngest Cleanie is almost done with the hose.)
Looking at her eyes above the mask, I see a sense of incredible focus.
- Right. I'm focused. - A sense of incredible focus.
It's my dopamine rush. I love cleaning.
When I was growing up, our bathroom was moldy.
My mother always managed to get rid of the mold.
When I saw that, I learned that I could get rid of mold...
with some cleaning.
- I learned that from my mom. - Yes, that's right.
(She cleans...)
(the inside of the toilet paper holder.)
It's my dopamine rush.
I never thought about cleaning the holder.
- Gosh. She's so detailed. - That's where bugs come from.
- I... - That's right.
(Just like she learned from her mom...)
Yes.
(Clean and thorough)
Then you have to remove the moisture.
(Tiptoeing)
(Splashing cold water on all of the walls)
(Humming)
Honestly, I bet it's cleaner than our body.
- Right. - Yes.
My gosh. I don't know what it is. But I'm getting hooked on this.
I should look into that.
How often do you deep-clean your bathroom like this?
- I do it every week. - Yes. Right.
I can totally relate to this.
But I clean the toilet bowl whenever I take a shower...
(I knew it.)
(Another cleaner can relate.)
- and every time I use the toilet. - That's...
- My gosh. - That's something else.
- Do you sometimes sleep in there? - Gosh, that's on another level.
Why do you clean that thoroughly?
I clean it to the point that I can sleep in there.
- Right. - Yes.
(This time, she grabs an orange towel.)
(She steps on top of the toilet.)
- We have the same cleaning towel. - It's good.
- Really? - Yes.
(Decalcomania)
Do the towels have different purposes?
- It's like... - I have face towels...
- Yes. - and bath towels.
- They're different towels? - They're different towels. Yes.
For me, towels, rags, and dish towels are all the same.
- Oh, no. - That's...
- Oh, that's... - So all your towels are rags.
(She's not done yet.)
- Yes! - Removing moisture is...
the most important part.
I always do that after taking a shower.
(Hopping)
The most important last step of cleaning the bathroom is...
removing moisture.
I remove moisture after every time I take a shower.
After cleaning the bathroom,
always use the squeegee to remove moisture.
Then your bathroom is twice as clean.
Removing moisture is the most important for cleaning enthusiasts.
Right. I don't know why, but watching her clean is satisfying.
(She's finally done cleaning the bathroom.)
It looks like a new house.
Her landlord must be so happy.
(Before and after the cleaning session)
Great.
- I don't see any difference. - Right?
- I don't see any difference either. - It looks the same.
- It's so clean. - It is.
- Just like that... - It's super clean.
- The fact that it looks the same... - Well, it's...
- is cooler. - Right.
- It's always clean. - Is it like being on a diet...
- all the time? - That's right.
- And the tiles... - No.
- That was meant for me, right? - No.
Let me clarify something.
That's your inferiority complex creeping in.
It is?
- I was trying to understand it... - Okay.
- from my point of view. - Okay.
I have an inferiority complex.
- I do too. - I do.
- It's easier when you admit it. - Of course.
- Everyone has it. - We all have it.
Great.
You have to turn on the fan...
- and close the door. - Right.
- You can't keep the door open. - Right.
- I see. Really? - I see.
(Gosh, I'm finally done.)
(She wraps it up perfectly.)
(Let me see.)
- What's that? - I checked off what I did.
That's nice.
(Marking the cleaning task done on the planner)
(Okay. I did it.)
(After she finishes cleaning,)
(she grabs her phone.)
Why don't you lie down?
I don't lie down again once I make the bed.
- Right. - I see.
- Not to lie down, - Yes.
- you sat there instead. - Yes.
(She's resting in front of the bathroom.)
(She quietly checks her phone.)
(Opening her banking app)
A banking app?
(Tapping)
What? You wired some money.
- Yes. - What?
What's going on?
I had a student loan.
But I paid off all of my student loans as of today.
- What? Really? - My gosh.
(Congratulations!)
Congratulations.
- I got paid from my part-time job. - Okay.
- What part-time job? - A part-time job?
- Pardon? - What part-time job?
I work part-time at a restaurant...
and as a babysitter.
Do you still work part-time?
Yes, I do.
Don't people recognize you?
A lot of people recognize me.
I had people come back after an hour when they saw me work...
just to give me vitamin supplements.
I really hope things work out for you.
- I agree. I want to root for you. - Yes. I'm sure you will.
It's been nine years.
It took a long time because I had to pay it back with my part-time jobs.
"Come and check this out." I once gave out flyers...
while wearing a cat costume.
I paid it back with my hard-earned money from my part-time jobs.
- Gosh. - That's amazing.
- Your parents didn't help you? - Seriously.
They asked me if I wanted their help.
But it was my education.
- My mom didn't attend the school. - Right.
- My gosh. - It's only right I paid it back.
My gosh, no.
- Usually, kids accept help. - I love her mindset.
They promise to pay it back twofold.
- You know? - That's usually the case.
It was my education, and my mom paid for it,
but I still skipped classes.
- And people don't pay it back. - Hey.
I did all of that. And I told my mom...
I was taking time off from school...
and asked her to give me the tuition.
- Ji Su, you're so cool. - That's really cool.
- Seriously. - Gosh, Ji Su.
It was my education. So...
- You're emotional. Great job. - My gosh. You did well.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
- What? - Give her some pocket money.
(Blinking)
- What am I? Her grandpa? - Come on.
- Why would I give her money? - Come on, give her some money.
- You can give her some money. - I don't have cash on me.
- I'll give it to you later. - Okay.
(Grandpa is the best.)
(She paid back the student loan in 9 years.)
- I'm reevaluating myself now. - She did that...
- while building her career. - I couldn't have done that.
(Thinking)
(She calls someone.)
What is it? Who are you calling?
- Hello. - Mom, what are you doing?
- Me? - Yes.
I'm home.
I just...
made the last payment of my student loan.
My goodness.
Great job, Ji Su.
Gosh, that must have been tough.
Ji Su.
You worked so hard to pay it off.
I'm sorry...
I couldn't help you more.
- Gosh, she's emotional too. - My gosh.
- My gosh. - I'm so proud of you, Ji Su.
No, you already helped me plenty.
(Choking up)
My goodness.
(You worked so hard.)
- Gosh. You must've worked hard. - Oh, my.
Oh, no. I cry easily.
(Sobbing)
- She paid it back in nine years. - I also cry easily.
- It's okay. - It must've bothered her mom.
The memories from that day are coming back.
- I see. - It's okay.
Hyun Moo will give you...
- pocket money. - That's right.
- How much should I give her? - He'll do everything.
He'll buy you a house too.
(Quickly trying to help her stop crying)
I'm debt-free now.
Yes, you're debt-free.
Ji Su, only good things will be in your future.
- Okay. - I'll root for you.
Thank you.
Don't thank me. I should thank you.
I'm sorry too.
Today, I'm going to buy some things I wanted to buy.
My gosh.
Buy whatever you want and eat whatever you crave too.
And do everything you couldn't do before. Okay?
Okay.
I'll buy you a lot of things later too.
Okay. Buy me a lot of things later.
Okay.
Thank you for everything, Mom.
This is a happy day for both of us. Right?
That's right.
Yes. Have a good day today.
Okay. I love you, Mom.
- Okay. Have a good day. - Okay.
- You too. - Thanks.
(She finishes the call with a warm goodbye.)
- My goodness. - Gosh, an experience like that...
- This is quite emotional indeed. - Right.
It was odd. I felt empty inside.
Actually, I didn't think I'd cry.
I know I cry easily. But I thought I would be full of smiles today.
"This is crazy. It's over!" I thought I'd celebrate like this.
"I did this."
"I was someone who could do this."
That was the first thought I had.
Then I felt empty...
- and thought of my mom. - Feeling empty is understandable.
You feel empty...
because you've worked hard.
When I hung up,
- the past nine years... - That's right.
flitted through my mind.
The part-time jobs flitted through my mind.
- Your parents must be proud. - Seriously.
- Seriously. - They must be very proud.
(Rushing over)
Gamja.
A cat consoles her.
- Gamja. - How did she come to her right now?
She comes to me whenever I cry.
(After consoling her mom,)
(she goes back to her place in a chic way.)
(Thanks to Gamja, she pulls herself together.)
(Heave-ho)
(She changes to go out.)
I guess she'll buy something.
(She packs her bag.)
(Let's go shopping.)
(Humming)
It's nice.
The weather is so nice.
There is something I want to do...
when I pay off my student loans.
It's buying unexpected items.
I want to buy the items I want without any worries.
(I'll buy everything I want today.)
I'm curious to see how Ji Su will flex.
Had it been like that
Maybe she'll only buy the cleaning supplies.
(Laughing)
I'm really curious to see what Ji Su will buy.
Let's clear the place.
See? She went to Daiso.
(Her eyes become lively.)
(What should I buy?)
(Her feet lead her to a place.)
(A cleaning supplies section?)
See? It's cleaning again.
I wasn't going to go there.
It's her idea of flexing.
All right.
(Let's see.)
(Sparkling eyes)
(Which product is better?)
Which one is better?
(I choose you.)
I'll remember the items Ji Su buys.
I'll buy them as well.
(This one...)
(and that one)
She is flexing.
She paid off her debts. It's a good day to flex.
I agree.
(Very satisfied)
(She takes out the grocery bag she has brought from home.)
(Flexing properly)
Will the total be about 50 dollars?
(18 items cost 35.5 dollars.)
I flexed.
I usually spend only ten dollars when I go to Daiso.
I usually spend only 10 dollars. Today, I spent 30 dollars.
I spent three times the money.
Thank you.
(I enjoyed overspending.)
Gamja.
Did she come home right away?
- Yes. - That's right.
Why didn't she eat anything?
- Mom told her to eat tasty food. - She came home really quickly.
- I wasn't used to spending money, - That's right.
so I didn't know where to go.
You should've eaten tasty food at a nice restaurant...
- That's right. - and bought clothes.
I rarely buy clothes.
- Really? - Yes.
I maybe buy one piece of clothing a month.
I'm not telling you to splurge.
But if there were items you liked, you should buy them...
- or try them on. - Think of your interests.
But you suppress your urges.
She has gotten used to it.
- That's right. - Yes.
- I don't have many clothes, - Nothing like that.
but I want to buy her clothes.
You should buy your own clothes.
- I just want to buy her clothes. - Seriously.
(Picking up)
(She sanitizes her phone upon coming home.)
- I can't believe it. - She is neat.
(She changes into comfortable clothes.)
(Rattling)
(It's time to eat dinner.)
(She takes out a scale.)
Will she measure the grams? She uses a scale.
(She pours in cream without hesitation.)
(She pours in the exact amount of sugar.)
Today, I want to bake something.
I'll make a strawberry cream cake.
- A strawberry cream cake? - A strawberry cream cake?
(That's incredible.)
What?
(Another appliance, an electric mixer, appears.)
She has skills from working part-time.
She knows how to use those appliances.
(Thanks to the appliance, the cream is whipped in no time.)
All right.
(Taking out)
(Moon-shaped bread)
You know what it is.
It's a nice tip.
- It's a nice tip. - That's right.
You use it as a sheet cake.
- Full Moon Cake. - I prepared it on purpose.
(She brushes on sugar water on the halved cake.)
She has everything.
I sometimes buy those kinds of things.
(She puts a heap of whipped cream on the top.)
(She puts fresh strawberries between the sheets.)
(She turns the turntable to spread the whipped cream.)
The cake is coming along.
- That's right. - It looks pretty.
It looks like an actual cake.
(Squeezing)
(Piping)
- Well done. - It's pretty.
(She wraps up with strawberry decorations.)
Good.
- Did you make that at home? - Yes.
- I'm impressed. - Anyone can make it.
(She puts the cake in the fridge...)
(and plops down.)
(I'm exhausted.)
(To be continued)
Is someone here?
Teacher? Mom?
(Ji Su runs over to get the door upon hearing the bell.)
Ji Su, hello.
(Stomping)
- Who is that? - Who is that?
My goodness.
- Dad, come on in. - Hello.
- Who is that? - My dad.
- Water. - Do you welcome your dad...
that warmly?
Your dad must love you so much.
There was a reason to celebrate,
so I invited Dad to my place.
Dad, thanks for the water.
- I only had one bottle left. - Really?
Dad always brings it because it's heavy.
(Oh, my)
- Right now, - So...
- it needs to be wiped down. - I'll do it.
- I need to taste it. - Chicken soup?
- Did you make chicken soup? - I know.
- No way. - When did you make that?
(She made tasty chicken soup earlier.)
- She boiled chicken. - She is diligent.
(Full of love)
- My goodness. - I made chicken soup.
- He must be so happy. - It's nearly done.
Where is Gamja?
- Under the table. - Where is Gamja?
- Gamja won't come out. - Let's see.
Gamja, it's good to see you.
It's good to see you.
- Dad, did you look behind you? - What?
- Say hello. - What?
- Hello. - Hello.
In 1, 2... In 1, 2, 3.
- I've seen him many times on TV. - We've seen you many times on TV.
- He is my dad. - Nice to meet you.
Hello. Let's do it one last time.
Hello.
It's so nice that you guys are like friends.
- I'll sit here. - It won't take long.
(Dad, please wait a second.)
Dad, yours is coming first.
Be careful.
(She scoops her dad's chicken soup first.)
- Is there yours as well? - Of course.
- Dad, this is mine. - Okay.
I hope you'll give me some meat.
What?
- I hope you'll give me some meat. - Okay.
My pot is small.
It didn't fit two chickens.
- I could only cook one chicken. - Hold on.
There is no meat whatsoever.
Give me your plate.
That's more than enough.
- Take one. - Okay.
- It looks legit. - Does it look legit?
Let's try it.
- The soup. - All right.
(She tries the soup first.)
The soup.
(Dad takes a bite.)
(I see.)
- Was it your first time making it? - Yes, it was my first time.
- Really? - It was my first time.
(Thumbs up)
- What? He gave a thumbs-up. - Is it tasty? Is it good?
You need to add salt.
Firstly, you've worked hard.
You've worked hard.
(Relieved)
Dad, you're eating with gusto.
He is enjoying his food.
He is eating with gusto.
- Dad eats with gusto. - Yes.
(Taking another bite)
- Today, - I heard it.
I paid off my student loans.
- That's right. - Yes.
Well done. Let's go.
Let's go. You've done so well.
(Proud)
You were a nominee at the Baeksang Arts Awards.
I felt very proud.
Of course, he felt proud.
- Winning an award wasn't important. - That's right.
I felt like I was dreaming.
You just need to enjoy yourself.
That's right.
I think I got these tendencies from you.
- Really? - Yes.
You're tenacious.
- You received a trophy at work. - Yes.
- Did you bring it? - I did. Yes.
I received a trophy.
- Do you want to see it? - I'll bring it.
(My goodness)
- Seriously, Dad. - Take a look.
(Dad's trophy for 30 years of service)
"The 30 years we've walked together..."
"and the future we'll face."
Director Choi Chang Ha.
Your dad needs a round of applause.
- Seriously. - At one company too.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Proud)
- Keep eating. - Okay.
I'll bring something.
Put yourself at ease.
(Hurrying over)
(Rummaging)
What?
- Dad. - Yes?
What? What's that?
(What? What's that?)
(Ta-da)
Daughters are the best.
- You're right. - What's that?
I made it myself.
(I made it for you, Dad.)
- When you go to a pricey place, - Thank you.
they give you a dessert with your name written on it.
I wrote this writing at the bottom.
(Cute)
Make a wish.
- A wish? - Yes.
Close your eyes. Don't say it out loud.
Let's make a wish together.
Okay.
(Closing his eyes)
(She prepared a cake with respect for her dad.)
(Clasping her hands together, she makes a wish with her dad.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you. Should I blow out the candle?
Yes.
(Blowing)
(Congratulations.)
- You know... - You're handsome.
(Embarrassed)
No other daughter is as nice as her.
Seriously. No other daughter is...
- as nice as her. - Right.
- She is the best. - Ta-da.
- Try the strawberry cake. - Okay.
Here.
(She cuts a big piece.)
Here. Give me a bite.
(After the dad takes a bite, the daughter takes a bite.)
My goodness.
- You could... - What do you think?
You could sell it.
I made it well, right?
- You could... - What do you think?
It'll be so nice to have...
a daughter with such incredible reactions.
- My goodness. - Dad. Time out.
Why was your reaction different when you had the chicken soup?
What?
- I could sell the cake, - It isn't like that.
but the chicken soup...
- He became flustered right away. - As for the chicken soup,
- My dad can't lie. - it should be seasoned a bit more.
- You said it was tasty. - It's tasty.
(Although he said it was tasty, he ate slowly.)
Seriously, Dad.
(He even sprinkled pepper behind his daughter's back.)
- I found the chicken soup tasty. - But... I found it tasty too.
You have a talent for making cakes.
"You have a talent for making cakes."
- I mean... - Your reactions are so different.
This is tasty.
- It's tasty, right? - Yes.
- It's tasty. - I found the chicken soup tasty.
It's tasty.
Where are you going after the meal?
- Me? Yes. - Are you going home?
Yes, I'm going home.
- I need to go and work part-time. - Okay.
- That day too? - Will you go and work part-time?
Take care. Good luck.
(Holding her hands tight)
You're the star of the day, so don't do anything.
- Thank you for the food. - Sit still...
and look outside the window.
- Enjoy the view. - I'll bring the plates to the sink.
- No, you can't. - Really?
- It's just that... - No.
- Seriously. - Dad, enjoy the view.
I'll look at Gamja.
- Guests at my place can't move. - Gamja.
- That's right. - I do everything.
- It's easier that way. - The guests are the kings.
You do things well by yourself.
- You do the dishes well. - Of course.
I can tell from her dad's eyes that he dotes on his daughter.
I'm ready to get married.
What?
He doesn't like it.
Tell him when you're seeing someone.
My dad tells me not to get married.
- Really? - He thinks I'm too good for anyone.
- For real? - Dads are like that.
- Why did you ask, "For real?" - What?
- I can't let this go. - Seriously.
(It's a misunderstanding.)
- Why did you ask, "For real?" - I'm sorry.
- This is... - Seriously.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry, Shin Young.
It's okay.
I'm done with the dishes.
- Are you done? - Yes.
You've become neater since moving out,
- right? - Of course.
If I don't do it, no one else does.
That's right.
Dad, I need to get ready for my part-time job,
- so you can leave first. - Okay.
All right.
Gosh, do you guys actually hug?
- Of course. - It was nice.
Dad, travel safely.
- Dad. - I'm glad I bought water.
- Bye. - I'll get going now.
Bye.
- My goodness. - What?
- I mean... - A kiss on the cheek.
A kiss on the cheek is rare.
- I haven't seen it in a while. - In your 20s...
- I haven't seen it in a while. - My goodness.
We hug our parents...
- or put our shoulders around them. - That's right. We do that much.
- Really? - But a kiss on the cheek is...
- Sons don't do that. - It's understandable.
- How about, "Dad, I love you?" - I say that often.
- Really? - I say that all the time.
I stopped saying "Dad, I love you..."
- in third grade. - Really?
(Very mature)
I wrote it in my letter from the army training center.
- The army training center? - I cried.
- When you came out... - You're less than human...
if you don't write that there.
- That's right. - Really?
It could be a test to see if you're human or not.
After getting drunk, I messaged my mom,
- "Mom, I love you." - Gosh!
She left me on read.
- She felt awkward. - That's right.
(Did she think it was a spam message?)
- Bye. - I'll get going now.
- Bye. - Thank you.
- It's such a heartwarming sight. - Thank you.
Such interactions are rare.
- Really? - Come again.
Dad does that to Mom.
- It makes sense. - That's right.
That's right.
Dad, take care.
(The sun sets.)
- I'm on my way to work part-time. - You're on your way.
(Taking big steps)
Today, I got to immerse myself...
in my life.
"I'm living diligently all day."
I felt that today.
There has been a major change after moving out.
- Mom and Dad aren't with me. - That's right.
- They aren't with you. - No one carries heavy items for me.
If I put my socks somewhere...
and look at the spot again after taking a short rest,
they're still there.
No one picks them up for me.
I learned that by heart.
That's why I'm learning to do things myself.
You need to do things yourself.
(She is building her own daily life.)
(She continues to fill her days.)
I want to work hard.
Do you keep studying?
- Yes, there are many lines. - On your way?
The lines.
(Ji Su's Happiness Is Sailing Smoothly)
I want to keep watching.
- How about the part-time job? - I wanted to watch her work.
- We enjoyed the video. - Seriously.
Thank you.
How did it feel to watch your daily life?
It was fascinating to see myself on TV.
Your continuous reactions...
- felt so genuine. - Yes, they were totally genuine.
That made me tear up even more.
- They were totally genuine. - Right.
- It was a truly independent life. - Seriously.
What Shin Young said on the show...
went viral on the internet.
- "Only you can help yourself." - No one else can do it.
Ji Su lives that life.
- I love it. - She is the perfect example.
I learn many things by watching Shin Young on TV.
She is like the adult version of myself.
Gosh, I'll need to stay alert and live well.
I'll need to do that.
(The adult becomes solemn.)
Personally, I thought...
- it was the essence of life. - I know.
Her daily life had the joys and sorrows.
"I Live Alone" needed...
- I know. - a guest like her.
When I star in an audition show once in a while,
I see people who have lived...
every day to the fullest.
- That's right. - If you live that way,
you'll have many materials...
you can use no matter what you do...
- in the future. - I know.
I think now is her time to use those materials.
- So... - She has strength.
Given her personality...
- You said such nice things. - It's my part-time job...
to pass the tissue paper today.
- You said such nice things. - My goodness.
I just want to let you know...
that you need to challenge yourself recklessly now.
I have the same advice.
You should find your tastes...
and focus on yourself.
"What do I like?"
"What do I want to do if I have money?"
I hope you'll think about that.
- You're living too diligently. - I agree.
You failed to win the Best Rookie Award,
but better awards will come your way.
Your words make me feel like...
- I've won an award. - But you need an actual award.
Forget about feeling like you've won an award.
I hate that the most.
When you're a nominee, they film you nonstop.
"You're the winner in my heart" is even more aggravating.
I hate that the most.
"You're the first-place winner in my heart."
That's the worst.
- I just want to win first place. - People don't think I deserve it.
- That's right. - Yes.
- That's exactly it. - Yes.
Win an award. Seriously.
- You'll have a nice life. - A very nice life.
We will root for you!
- Good luck! - Good luck!
(I Live Alone)
(Thorough Cleaning)
(Sung Hwan is fast asleep.)
(Tossing and turning)
Gosh, the time is...
(He barely manages to get himself up.)
- He slept outside! - So he sleeps outside.
(Unlike with the fairly dull color from the past,)
(the rooftop looks a lot brighter in pink.)
The rooftop is in pink now!
Right. I love pink.
(He has everything that is needed to sleep outside.)
(He also has items...)
Gosh, check out the vibes.
- Gosh, they're items from the past. - That's great.
(that bring up the vibes.)
(Sung Hwan's brand new hideout)
From around April to the middle of June,
I sleep outside from time to time depending on the weather.
- That sounds great. - I'm so jealous.
It will feel cozy. I'm so jealous.
I hear songs on the radio.
I'm not sure which direction it comes from,
- but I can feel the breeze. - That must feel nice.
I personally also like the smell...
- of the mosquito coil. - The mosquito coil!
I love it when these three things are felt.
I think that is why I sleep outside from time to time.
(He sleeps on the rooftop from time to time!)
(Which channel should I listen to today?)
We saw this scenery back when we were in elementary school.
There were men who looked just like that.
It feels exactly like "Under the Same Roof."
Right!
It feels like the house from back then.
Right.
(On one side of the cozy rooftop,)
Gosh, the ice still hasn't melted.
(Father Ku takes something out.)
- The ice still hasn't melted. - Cassia seed tea!
- With that, - Sometimes, I...
you can mix in rice and make it cold.
You can eat it with cucumber kimchi or aged kimchi.
They should be cut vertically.
- Get used to it, Dowoon. - Gosh.
- It tastes great like that. - Right.
- Focus on her words. - That sounds amazing.
- She says a lot of great things. - Can I put on...
my AirPod on the left?
- Just the left. - You can't do that.
You can never do that. You have to...
- listen to her. - That will make me feel upset.
I'll still be able to listen.
- I just listened to her, - It will taste amazing like that.
but I can picture things around my mouth.
- Just like that. - The kimchi is torn like this.
- After wrapping it around... - Were the two of you close?
- They're like siblings. - No.
We met each other for the first time through I Live Alone.
We get along with each other so well.
They feel like high school friends.
- We're the Pepper Siblings. - Right.
Right. We both love pepper.
(Picking up)
(Pouring)
(He starts with a cold glass of cassia seed tea.)
The vibes, Sung Hwan!
I love the vibes.
(On the open rooftop,)
(he enjoys the morning of early summer.)
(Humming)
Gosh, Dad!
- Soon Dol's father! - Dad! Father!
- Where's Soon Dol? - Mom wants you to come down!
(Is that so?)
(While ignoring his wife's call,)
(he grabs the instant coffee.)
(Pouring the cold instant coffee)
Instant coffee with ice!
Right. The ice melted as I made it the day before.
That's amazing.
(A sweet charge of morning caffeine)
Dipping some sponge cake into that is the best!
- I'm serious. - I just want it separately.
You should give that a try.
How are we supposed to remember all of that?
- Get used to it, Dowoon. - Right.
I love it.
- You say you love everything! - I love the vibes.
Grow out your hair just on the right side.
(Joking)
Then I'll move to his left.
(His happy tea time comes to an end.)
(He gets his things and hurries down.)
I have a lot to do.
(I'm busy.)
First of all...
(He turns on the lights of his bedroom first.)
Wait. What's that?
(What are those things placed on one side of the wall?)
It's the Ku Zone. A place of my own.
After walking 446km,
I placed the outfit I wore on the wall.
- I see. - Mr. Ku Zone.
We can do it!
(The moments of the cross-country march)
My shoes are placed at the bottom.
I signed them myself. I wrote down "446km," the distance I went,
and my name, "Ku Sung Hwan."
When I open my eyes in the morning,
it makes me think, "I can do anything today."
That's the thought I get every morning...
- after setting up that spot. - The Ku Zone.
That's so impressive.
(Full of respect)
(Grabbing)
(He throws down the blanket after curling it up.)
(Is he also taking out the mattress cover?)
- The mattress cover? - Gosh!
Thank you for serving me for all this time, mattress.
- Are you changing your mattress? - That must be it.
With how much I weigh,
the springs pop out after around three years.
- It's of no use after four years. - Right.
But as that mattress stayed with me for five years,
it was like a soldier that fought 1,000 battles.
- That was how much it went through. - Really?
There will be parts that sink in after that long.
(After many fierce battles...)
It has scars everywhere.
It's full of scars.
So mattresses are consumables.
- Of course. - They have to be changed.
They have to be changed.
My friend who lived with me...
peed on it many times...
- when she was young. - Right.
- Puppies do that. - And...
there are vomit stains as well.
After much consideration,
I decided to...
go for a replash.
- That's why I'm going to change it. - What's "replash?"
You should replash your mind.
The reason for that... Let's move on.
(The replash is going smoothly.)
My gosh.
Gosh, Kkotbun.
(Tapping)
(I've used it for a long time.)
(Heave-ho!)
(Grabbing)
(He cleans the bottom of the bed while he's at it.)
The bottom of the bed looks really clean.
I cleaned the bottom...
- You did? - from time to time.
When you start coughing for some reason in a clean house,
- you have to check down there. - Right.
Gosh, there we go.
Sung Hwan is so neat.
(He heads to the living room after cleaning the room.)
(He makes a call to someone.)
- I have arrived. - I'll go down, sir.
- Okay. - Right.
(Let's hurry down.)
(Hurrying down)
(Opening)
(Looking around)
Oh, hello.
- You're from the mattress company. - Right.
- The mattress is here. - It's a pleasure to meet you.
You feel this excitement when you bring in new furniture.
- Right. I felt so excited. - Right.
- It feels like a new start. - A new start.
Right.
(They bring it down slowly.)
- We'll try to bring it down first. - Gosh.
- It was really heavy. - It must be really heavy.
You bought a big one.
The width of the mattress was 1.5m.
The width of the windows of my house is 1m.
It was impossible to bring in through the windows.
- I think it will be possible. - It's impossible.
I've tried everything to make it work.
I explained everything in advance...
that we had to carry it up...
There's no elevator at my place.
- from the... - It must be really tough...
- first floor. - to go up with that.
As I feel bad about this, I'll move to the tougher side.
(He even brought down the man of 100kg.)
- The Rainbow Cheonha Champion. - Gosh!
- That's impressive. - I'm sorry, Jang Woo.
(Rainbow Cheonha Champion, Ku Sung Hwan)
(I'll use more of my strength.)
Then you should lift it up from the bottom for us.
- Should I do that? - Yes.
One, two, three.
- That must be tough. - Gosh!
It must be hard as there's no place to hold onto.
This is really heavy!
I'm sorry.
We'll bring it down here.
(He feels flustered as it's heavier than he thought.)
(Bringing his head down)
- The fifth floor? - Yes.
- The fifth floor. - Gosh.
- I'm sorry. - It's tough without an elevator.
- Turn to the side. - Got it. I turned to the side.
A complete turn.
Gosh.
It's tough to turn at the corners.
The mattress is this big in that tight space.
Right.
(Heave-ho!)
- Just give it a push. - Right.
- One, two... Yes. - Shall we go?
I didn't have the skills.
You have to have great teamwork.
One, two, three!
(Heave-ho!)
- Turn it around. - Right.
This must be done four more times. Gosh.
Gosh, that must be exhausting.
Just a moment.
He's going to eat a lot as he used a lot of strength.
- I'm 100 percent certain. - I can imagine it already.
One, two, three!
(Why is this so heavy?)
(He pushes it up the stairs after carrying it on his shoulder.)
- One, two, three! - One, two...
(He pushes with all his might from the bottom.)
(Struggling)
One, two.
(The weight of the mattress goes all on Sung Hwan.)
- One, two, three! - But the owner seems to be...
such a nice person.
At the first floor,
many would start with, "There's no elevator?"
- Right. - I felt so bad about it,
so I told him in advance...
- that there wasn't an elevator. - That there wasn't one.
He said two men would be more than enough for it.
- That was how it started. - He thought it would be okay.
He said it would be okay, but it was heavier than I thought.
That's really tough to move.
Gosh.
(They arrive at the 3rd floor.)
- Just push it. - Right.
This way.
(Leaning)
(Ringing)
I pressed it by mistake.
I was opening the mattress. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
As there was no space,
I ended up pressing the doorbells.
One, two, three!
(Groaning)
(After wrestling with the mattress,)
(he's drenched in sweat.)
Just a moment, sir.
I can't breathe.
- Gosh. - I'm sorry.
(Panting)
(While Sung Hwan catches his breath and wipes his sweat...)
- It's his unlucky day. - I'm dying.
I'm about to die.
I'm so sorry, sir.
I didn't think it would be this tough.
I thought the window could come apart. I'm sorry.
Isn't it better to bring it up to the rooftop...
and bring it down one floor?
(Isn't it better to bring it up to the rooftop...)
(with the ladder truck and bring it down one floor?)
- You're right. - Instead of doing that.
- You should try thinking once. - Right.
- You're so smart. - No.
Hold on.
I should call you before I move to a different place.
Right.
(Impressed)
- Why tell me that now? - I didn't know about it.
I didn't think of that.
He's a smart one.
(What have I done?)
One, two, three!
(He's suffering as he wasn't able to think about the rooftop.)
We're almost there, sir.
You must have a cold drink with him after this.
It's really hot outside as well.
It's really hot.
- We'll move straight in. - Right.
- Slowly. - I'm pushing it.
Gosh, the angle...
Gosh, it went in! It's going to work.
The real problem starts here.
- My goodness. - We can do it.
It will be tough to go through that door.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
Hold on. I'll give it a try.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(Startled)
Hold on. I'll give it a try.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(Startled)
You're going to destroy everything.
What happened to the intercom system?
(The intercom system got attacked by Sung Hwan's weight.)
I'll try to pull it upward.
(Shaking)
(The intercom system reveals itself.)
Gosh, the intercom system.
- It looks like it broke off. - It's okay.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
These moments are really annoying.
It's okay.
(Worried)
I don't use the intercom system anyway.
It's okay.
- I'll take a look after this. - Right.
Pull it up from there.
Right. One, two.
(They're losing more and more strength.)
They made it!
One, two!
- Gosh, they brought it up. - They made it!
(They squeeze out everything they have...)
(and finally make it to the house.)
- Gosh. - They did it.
- Nice one. - There's a sense of gladness.
- That was intense. - Right.
Take a seat for a while. Sir.
Sir.
- Let's rest together. - That happens.
You collapse after that.
Look at the two of them sitting together.
(Laughing)
I'll get you a drink! Stay right here.
Stay right there. I'll get you a drink.
- Have a seat. - Thank you.
Gosh.
Gosh, my forearms feel sore.
My hands are shaking.
I can't seem to catch my breath.
(Exhausted)
Gosh.
- The mattress... - They look like co-workers.
Hyun Moo.
- They look like co-workers. - Hyun Moo.
It was possible because it was me.
- If you were the one to... - It would be impossible for him.
I would've moved it to the rooftop.
I would've used my brain first.
Gosh, he's so annoying.
- One, two, three! - One, two, three!
(They finish up after a short break.)
Awesome!
(It gets placed on the frame.)
It looks like a bunk bed!
- Why is the mattress so thick? - Why is it so high up?
- It's so nice. - It's really high up!
- It's this thick. - Right.
Thank you. You went through so much because of me.
There we go.
Gosh, this feels so light.
That one would feel like nothing after that.
(The mattress that went through many years is brought out.)
Gosh, thank you.
- Thank you, sir. - Thank you.
- I'll get going now. - I'll use it well.
- I won't go too far. - Right.
Thank you, sir!
- Gosh! - Gosh!
(He returns home.)
Gosh.
- Gosh! - That's sweat?
The sweat on his bottom... Gosh!
That's not sweat.
- My pants... - Then...
did you let go?
(Then did you let go?)
That must be my sweat.
- Right. It's his sweat. - It's sweat.
I didn't know.
(Both of his shoulders are wet as well.)
It's fascinating how you're sweating here.
Right.
His sweat glands must be on his shoulders and buttocks.
(His sweat glands must be on his shoulders and buttocks.)
I don't have any armpit sweat.
(I don't have any armpit sweat.)
Have your sweat glands moved here?
I don't have any sweat here. Try touching it. It's fine.
No, thanks.
(Gosh!)
- He looks appalled. - Wait.
If I touch it...
(Sizzling)
- It might start sizzling. - Gosh!
(My fingers might be in danger.)
But I sweat like that as well.
You sweat like that as well?
I don't have any armpit sweat.
I sweat with my back, bottom, and feet.
- You two are the same. - I'm serious.
- Aren't you two long-lost siblings? - The sweat in bottom...
- We're very similar. - Go for a DNA test.
I got surprised by the spots of where he sweats.
Sweating with your bottom isn't something to be embarrassed about.
Gosh!
You're the one who's making him feel embarrassed!
I fully revealed that I do that as well.
- Don't be embarrassed about it. - Okay!
- It's just sweat. - Well...
(He heads to the mattress that made his bottom sweat.)
Gosh, the brand new mattress is going to get ruined!
- I didn't know. - No!
- Gosh! - I didn't know it was wet.
(He seals it with his bottom sweat right away.)
Please do me a great favor.
(Please do me a great favor.)
(Struggling)
Why are you dragging that?
- This one as well? - The sofa is thrown out as well?
I've spent so much time with you as well.
As it couldn't handle my weight,
the sofa was beaten down as well.
If I use the bow and arrow as an example,
it got hit by 10,000 arrows.
(One arrow)
It sinks down like this.
- Just like that. - Right.
- It has sunken down like that. - Right.
How can a sofa break down because of the weight?
When it gets used for a long time,
- it will start rattling. - Is that so?
- It becomes uncomfortable. - I feel so grateful for her.
- I totally understand you. - You're the best!
I changed sofas once a year when I weighed a lot.
Really?
I wanted to refresh everything and bring some change.
He cleans the floor first. He's so neat.
Yes, sir!
- Hello. - It's another delivery.
- Right. - We have arrived.
Right.
Hello, sir.
- Hello. - Hello.
- This one. - Right.
- What? - The ladder truck.
- The ladder truck can be used. - The sofa fit through the windows.
- It's the right size. - Right.
- Right. - The mattress couldn't fit.
- Right. - Right.
One, two.
(Heave-ho!)
(It's time to send away the sofa he got attached to.)
I'll place it. Hold on.
(It goes down at once with the ladder truck.)
- The ladder truck is the best. - Right. It's the best thing.
(Empty)
Gosh.
(He checks the empty space without the sofa.)
You must've gotten attached to it with the dog you raised.
Right. That is why I'm trying to change everything.
Right.
Gosh, goodbye!
You get attached to furniture.
- I got attached to it. - Right.
It feels strange when you throw out your furniture.
- It felt strange. - Right.
- Right. - You get attached to furniture.
It must be coming up.
Hold on. Okay. I'll pull it.
Gosh, this is also heavy.
Right. We'll hold it from this side.
There we go.
(It gets placed at the same spot of the previous sofa.)
There we go! Thank you.
That's perfect.
(Letting go of the sofa that seemed like it got 10,000 shots)
(Done changing into a new sofa in the same style)
He got the same sofa.
- Why did you get the same one? - I mean...
It must be really important...
- to have a cup holder for you. - Of course.
I'm also very sensitive about having storage...
- on both sides of the sofa. - That one has everything.
- There's a storage at the bottom. - That's right.
- Because you need to store food. - It needs a storage.
- We'll take a photo of the sofa. - Sure.
- Just the sofa, please. - Oh, just the sofa?
Oh, okay.
- That was... - My gosh. That day...
That's really embarrassing.
- Thank you. - He's acting like a total celeb.
- Thank you. - Bye.
(Saying goodbye to the installer awkwardly)
Gosh, this... This is crazy, seriously.
(Plopping down)
(Amazed)
- That must be nice. - That's nice.
(Super satisfied)
Happiness is found...
- in the simplest things. - Of course.
My goodness. This is nice.
Since I've cleaned the house...
(As he's refreshed...)
Is he going to do something there?
Right around here.
I always leave the windows open every day.
- I don't like feeling stuffy. - That's right.
So there's so much dust on the balcony.
Since more dust came in with the new furniture,
I decided to clean the balcony.
(Planning to clean the balcony thoroughly)
Gosh, this isn't some kind of barbecue restaurant.
- Why is there... - Gosh.
- I was really shocked. - The grill plate...
- It's fantastic. - You have all kinds...
- of grill plates. - Gosh, it's a cauldron lid.
(Here's another grill plate.)
You can make doenjang jjigae with it.
Doenjang jjigae? You know it.
- How many grill plates do you have? - This is crazy.
Do you use different plates depending on your mood?
- No, it depends on the meat. - It depends on the cuts.
(Filling the washbin with water...)
(after removing all the stuff on the balcony)
(Then he adds dish soap into it.)
I highly recommend diluting dish soap...
into water when you do cleaning.
I've tried using everything like baking soda, vinegar,
and bleach.
I think it's best to use dish soap.
- Is that so? - That's right.
Oh, really? Like that?
I'm lifting things a lot today.
(To the balcony with a washbin filled with dish soap water)
Gosh!
(Stubborn grime stuck to the floor)
(I'll clean them all today.)
You're going to clean them.
- For cleaning the floor? - That's right.
Gosh, how refreshing.
- You feel great when you do that. - Yes, when you spray water.
Gosh, this is nice.
Oh, you're using your hands?
- No, using an exfoliating towel. - An exfoliating towel?
- I'm using that because... - You know your stuff.
you can clean every nook and cranny...
- compared to using a brush... - That's right.
because you can use your fingers.
(Scrubbing hard)
(Sung Hwan exfoliates every nook and cranny.)
I feel great when I clean like that because...
- The grime gets washed away. - the grime gets washed away.
(Feeling refreshed)
Look at the built-up grime.
(Hopping)
- That must be really slippery. - It is.
That's why you need to squat down.
This feels great.
Gosh, it gets washed off well.
- A steel wool scrubber too? - With the towel...
and steel wool scrubber...
(Sliding)
(Slipping)
- Oh, no! - Goodness!
- Your head! - Watch your head!
My gosh!
You almost died.
You survived because you gained fat on your back. Otherwise...
If it were CODE KUNST, he'd have hit the back of his head.
- If it were CODE KUNST, - The back of his head...
- he'd have broken his back. - That was dangerous.
I hold a third-degree black belt in judo.
Those who did judo like me and Shin Young...
Because I did judo,
- I did a breakfall right away. - That wasn't a breakfall.
- You just fell. - You were shocked.
- It wasn't a breakfall. - It wasn't. You just slipped.
A breakfall.
(What just happened?)
Gosh, the breakfall.
Thanks to the breakfall...
If I hadn't learned how to do breakfalls,
I'd have died.
(Shall I rinse off now?)
(Splash)
You should've connected a hose.
I can't connect a hose.
- There's no... - No. In the sink,
- In the sink... - there's a water supply line.
- You can connect a hose there. - Yes.
- Because that's a lot of work. - When he does cleaning next time,
CODE KUNST should visit.
You can give me orders.
- I will... - Then I'll share my knowledge.
No. You can share knowledge too,
- but just tell me what to do. - Oh, I can...
- just tell you what to do? - Yes, on the sofa.
Sounds good.
Until it dries...
(Let me wash until the floor dries.)
Let me wash.
It feels refreshing.
It's so clean.
It's shining.
- That gives you so much pleasure. - That's amazing.
(Sung Hwan is also washing and polishing up.)
It'll be dried fast as the windows are open.
It dries off soon.
Gosh, how refreshing.
(Feeling refreshed)
(Humming)
Honey
(Digging through)
You too...
Let's go.
(Going outside with a bunch of clothes)
Honey
Goodness.
Write down the registration number on a piece of paper.
Where's the registration number? Oh, here it is.
(He took the disposal registration number before leaving.)
Two, two, three. All right.
(He stuck it on the mattress and sofa without forgetting.)
- Oh, you can just do that? - Right.
People write the numbers these days.
- You need to write down the number. - Right.
- That's nice. - We used to put a sticker on it.
- I know. - Yes.
- Wait. You're here. - I'm here.
I thought you had a field day.
(Sung Hwan is greeting someone warmly?)
- Wait. - I'm here.
You're here.
I thought you had a field day.
- Didn't you have a field day? - No, tomorrow... Today...
We just trained today.
Then we timed it.
Who is that?
That's right. It's him.
- Mr. Ddol. - It's Mr. Ddol.
(I remember him!)
(He met Mr. Ddol next door last time too!)
- Then tomorrow... - He became fitter.
- Yes. - He looks firmer.
Let's go ride together next time.
How far do you go?
I'll go wherever you want.
- You think you can handle me? - Yes.
- "You think you can handle me?" - I'm practically an ironman.
(I'm practically an ironman.)
Let's go ride together when the weather gets better.
- I'll get going now. - Goodbye.
You say that to everyone you meet.
"You think you can handle me?"
- Hello, sir. - Hey.
- You're well, right? - Yes.
It's been so long.
- My hands are full, so... - Hey.
- He's like the unofficial mayor. - I know.
They're all neighborhood guys to me.
- A selfie... - Yes.
- Stay healthy, sir. - Sure.
I'll call you. Bye.
Gosh, I haven't seen him in a long while.
Forty-six years? That means he's...
- That's right. - Yes.
(He kept walking while saying hi to his neighbors.)
- Hello. - Goodness.
(He said hi to her last summer as well.)
(Sung Hwan's go-to dry cleaner)
- This needs to be dry-cleaned. - Yes.
This needs to be ironed.
I think you have...
- one of my clothes here. - Right.
I'll take them together when these are done.
- Together? - Yes, together.
- I should've brought it. - Have two of these.
An ice pop.
Have one of this too.
Gosh, you're so warm-hearted.
They always give me lots of things...
- like food when I visit. - Goodness.
Then I'd give them some whenever I go there.
And this.
(He shares ice cream and bread today like usual.)
This one.
Gosh, you shouldn't.
(Sung Hwan shares generously.)
Something smells nice.
I made some toast for lunch.
Would you like one?
- Toast? - I made a lot.
- Toast? - Yes.
Then shall I taste it a little?
Don't just eat a little. Eat a lot.
You should eat. That's right.
- You like such food the most. - I do.
- Toast, burger... - A burger, yes.
I had a burger today.
Gosh.
Gosh, this is nice.
I mean...
Gosh, toast...
- That's... - Gosh.
- Gosh, it's the classic toast. - Homemade toast.
- It looks so good. Right? - You know, right?
- With margarine... - Margarine, yes. Exactly.
With lots of sugar.
When I come into your hideout...
Gosh! Look at this.
(The lady takes something out from the fridge.)
Is this "Under the Same Roof" from the 1980s?
- This is... - That's the best with toast.
So it was real.
- It's a must-have combination. - I like old-style bottles.
Then I will...
Since she gave it to me, even though she made it for the meal,
- I should eat it with gusto. - This is great.
(Taking a big bite)
- It's so good. - It's good, right?
- It's so good. - Do you want me to cut it?
It's nothing fancy,
- but it's really good. - That's the best.
It's not because I'm hungry.
It's savory, indeed.
(Adding sugar on top this time)
- You should have some. - With sugar.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
How did you know that I made some toast?
I didn't know.
It won't change now?
That dish and the drink...
- They're all classic. - That's right.
- They're the originals. - Yes, totally.
- Totally. It's so nice to see. - That's the best.
It's therapeutic.
How are your knees?
They are getting better. Because I lost weight...
- Right. - When I went trekking,
it was a little hard.
The knee cartilage...
was torn.
I walked with the torn cartilage, so it was hard.
After seeing you, I wanted to give it a try. These days,
I'm working really hard.
I'm working really hard, but it's not that easy.
You look a lot better...
- than the last time I saw you. - Really?
- You definitely look better. - He lost a bit of weight.
- It looks like he did. - He did lose weight.
You lost so much weight. You look gaunt.
Even after losing weight, I'm still 95kg.
- But you're big-built. - You're big-built.
You're big-built.
- But... - You're big-framed.
Because they're old, they called me big-framed.
I'll take this from home.
(The knees of a big-framed man are creaky.)
- Gosh, ma'am. - Goodness.
I enjoyed it so much. What do I do?
What do you mean?
- It's good that you enjoyed it. - Goodness.
I always get treated by you,
- like ramyeon. - No.
I'll come pick it up...
- when the rest are done. - Sure.
- Thank you. - Bye.
- Bye. - Bye. Thank you.
Gosh, the weather...
The weather... I hope it doesn't rain.
(He arrives home after taking a walk around the neighborhood.)
Gosh, I'm starving.
(Taking it)
(He took out a huge tray like usual.)
- And then... - You must have a tray like that...
for your convenience.
(Opening the fridge after taking out the tray)
(Picking)
This and...
(He carefully selected the ingredients for dinner.)
Let's make it delicious.
(Rummaging)
Wait. Is he making budae jjigae? Or tteokbokki?
All right.
(Getting fully prepared with an apron and gloves)
(This is great.)
- One-pot tteokbokki. - Gosh. That's it.
- What's that? Vertically... - You can tell from the pot alone?
Wait. You should make it vertical.
- Jjajang? - It's black bean paste.
You're making jjajang tteokbokki?
Adding chili oil too.
(Pouring chili oil on top)
I bought garaetteok on the way home.
It's rabokki with brisket, jjajang,
garaetteok, udon, and ramyeon.
- What? It's ramyeon and what? - You're eating all those?
BJ... BJG...
BJGRU rabokki?
It's BJGRU rabokki.
BJGRU?
(Let's stir-fry it well.)
(Stirring)
The black bean paste tastes better if you stir-fry it in oil.
- With chili oil, it's even better. - That's right.
With a sharp kick.
It's all set.
(Grabbing the brisket)
- Gosh, brisket. - It's better to use brisket...
- because it has more oil... - That's right.
than other meat.
- The savory oil... - That's right.
from beef comes out.
Your life and mine...
- are similar. - They're similar.
- They're really similar. - They're the same.
(After adding lots of brisket...)
(Sprinkling chili powder that will cut through the greasiness)
(Adding green onion and garlic according to his taste)
(Amazed)
The smell is crazy good.
It looks good.
Cut it thinly.
That way, the meat juice comes out, and the taste becomes richer.
If you boil the ramyeon noodles separately and mix them with it,
that becomes jjajangmyeon.
Add garaetteok.
(Adding garaetteok and fish cake on top of the stir-fried sauce)
You must add ramyeon seasoning.
Yes, ramyeon seasoning.
(Adding lots of pepper, which he likes)
- You must add pepper. - Pepper is a must.
(Egg and cheese)
(He doesn't stop adding ingredients.)
You must add cheese.
(Lastly, he pours an ox bone broth.)
Gosh, look how chili oil rises up.
That's it.
(BJGRU rabokki is ready.)
(Dinner prep is all done.)
(Pulling out a wet wipe)
(Wiping)
If chili oil splatters,
- That's right. - it could leave grease stains.
- I feel... - I must wipe it right away.
Watching you...
made me the most relaxed.
(Bonding over cleaning after cooking)
Gosh!
(The chili oil splattered.)
I was already annoyed.
Isn't that okay?
You can't wipe it off if it stays for too long.
If it stays, no matter how hard I wipe,
- That's right. - it smears.
- That's right. - Yes. I agree with that.
(He quickly took out a mini scrub brush before it smears.)
Oh, he can't even stand that.
My gosh.
This is nice. It's so relaxing.
Even if you wipe like that, it takes less than five minutes.
It's nothing shocking. It takes less than five minutes.
It takes no time.
All right. It's all set.
(Clean)
(Rummaging)
(A handheld portable fan?)
- Gosh, for real? - No way.
(Drying off water with a handheld portable fan)
(Shining without a single stain)
It looks like he polished it to a shine.
It looks new.
All set! Perfect.
If it gets messy, you can wipe it right away.
That's the most important.
But what's even more important is drying it.
If you don't dry it,
- it becomes stained. - That's right.
It feels nice if it shines.
Try this. Wipe it with a dry towel,
and then use a dishcloth...
that absorbs water at once.
- If you use that once... - Oh, I do wipe with it.
It doesn't leave fingerprints. You don't have to do that.
Still, I do that just in case.
I see. It doesn't take long.
- The thing is... - Or leave the range hood on.
- If you listen to them carefully, - I left it on.
they don't listen to each other at all.
- They keep going on. - I mean, in the end...
- We're just saying what we want. - They're trying to beat each other.
- No, that's not true. - They wouldn't agree.
- We're on different wavelengths. - We are...
- It's more like sharing info. - Yes, we're sharing info.
"That's true, but..."
(Lifting the tray filled with ingredients)
All right.
(I should go up since I'm done cleaning up.)
(Careful)
(Heave-ho)
- Gosh. - This is almost like...
You have a table used in restaurants.
I have many things that are used in restaurants.
All right.
(Placing the pot on the gas stove)
(Clicking)
(The heat is turned on.)
(This is good.)
(Soon, the broth starts boiling.)
(Grabbing ramyeon)
- This is the real jjajang rabokki. - It's fantastic.
Rabokki.
Gosh, the smell of jjajang...
is rising up.
(Adding udon next)
Oh, my.
This is good.
(The noodles are getting cooked while absorbing the broth.)
- Gosh. - This is to die for.
Gosh, this is crazy.
It really looks like...
- a tteokbokki place. - That's crazy.
Gosh, the pickled radish looks good.
The seasoned pickled radish.
(A full BJGRU rabokki spread)
It looks as good as a restaurant in Sindang-dong.
No, a restaurant in Sindang-dong...
- is much better. - Seriously.
It's what you buy with the money you earned,
- so it's a privilege of a grown-up. - That's right.
The ramyeon and udon I like.
You should've added glass noodles...
- to that. - And garaetteok.
But glass noodles absorb the soup too much.
- I see. - Gosh.
- The chili oil... - He isn't listening to her again.
He doesn't approve of her at all.
- Sung Hwan, will you follow me out? - No, that's not true.
- I... No! - I'll just whisper in your ear.
- I'm saying it absorbs soup a bit. - He never accepts it.
- Spare me a moment, Sung Hwan. - He never listens.
- Come out to the hallway for a bit. - But...
There's a spot with no security camera.
Gosh, it's all set.
(BJGRU rabokki is ready without a flaw.)
(Gulping)
That's crazy. The garaetteok looks crazy good.
(Taking a bite)
(Nodding in approval)
It's so good.
(This time, he picks up a handful of noodles.)
It looks so good.
Gosh, he mixed the noodles.
- That's udon and ramyeon. - And ramyeon.
- And ramyeon. - They have different textures.
- It's udon and jjajangmyeon. - That's right.
You should've added glass noodles to the combination.
He doesn't want to. He doesn't like glass noodles.
- No! I'll try it next time. - You don't like them?
You should get one raw noodle and chew it in front of her.
I'll chew them in front of you.
To that texture... Gosh.
(They seem to be unable to reach an agreement on glass noodles.)
(Taking a bite of the udon and ramyeon combination)
(Slurping)
- I'm jealous. - That must be good.
I'm so hungry.
(Slurping)
(Glaring)
He got a spark in his eyes.
That's it. One should eat like that.
The udon and ramyeon combination sounds good.
Personally,
there's a number I'm confident with. It's 100.
"How heavy are you?" "I weigh 100kg."
It gives off confidence.
"I weigh around 90kg."
When I say that, I don't look so good.
That's my opinion.
So when I do pull-ups,
it looks cool when I'm 100kg.
I weigh around 94kg now.
When I did trekking, I weighed around 95kg.
Before, I'd hit 100kg in no time,
but now, it's hard to go back to 100kg.
I think the number 100 is cool.
(The cool number 100 he can't seem to reach)
What a thing to worry about.
To you, a man ought to...
- weigh 100kg? - Yes, from 100kg to 105kg.
(Slurping aggressively)
(A little bit more...)
You should stop at 100kg.
(Worried)
(Chewing tenaciously to reach 100kg)
- You finished it? - Of course.
It's only a few bites.
(Taking something)
You must wrap up with fried rice.
- Goodness. - You know your stuff.
Nice! I was almost disappointed.
- Gosh, it's nice. - Nice.
Laver flakes!
(Sprinkling laver flakes as well)
You become really smart when you eat.
- He's a genius in that field. - I know.
(Grabbing)
What is that?
(Curious)
I use that when I press pork rinds.
That's the pork rind presser!
(He knows how to eat.)
(Amazed)
- That's right. - Now we're on the same page.
(A dramatic agreement)
When you make scorched rice,
- For real? - if you use that...
You can use that to make hotteok at home.
When you grill pork rinds, they pop,
- so you press them with that. - I knew it.
You have that at home too?
- I do. - Of course she does.
- They're on the same page. - Everyone has an expertise.
(Pressing hard)
That's it.
My love, cheese.
- I love adding cheese. - Cheese!
(If you add plenty of cheese on top,)
(you get fried rice worth 100 points!)
(Happy)
I wonder how it'd taste with cheese on top of jjajang teokbokki.
(I should eat it before it gets cold.)
(Gosh, it's hot.)
A tiger moth flies into the flame...
because it knows it's drawn to it.
I wanted to eat it,
so without realizing,
I took a bite despite knowing that it'd burn me.
He's flying into it.
(Swallowing)
It's too hot.
(Shocked)
(Despite that, the 95kg tiger moth flies into it.)
(Only if I can reach the cool weight of 100kg...)
He has a goal of reaching 100kg, that's why.
(Groaning)
- It must be good. - Because it's too good...
It's only delicious when you have it hot.
(Scraping)
The last bit. The scorched rice.
(The last spurt toward 100kg)
Where did it all go?
(Without realizing it, he finished the fried rice.)
(Gosh, that was a good meal.)
(Here we go.)
(After the meal, he lies down on the wooden platform.)
(Putting his leg up)
(Enjoying his free time with a gentle breeze)
- That's true happiness. - I love it.
A day that felt familiar yet completely new.
It was really strange. I felt good.
Actually, for a few months,
I was a bit...
(Emotionally, he was a little...)
I had a hard time emotionally.
It could be because I got new things...
and the environment changed.
I'm somewhat excited.
I feel like there will be more good days to come.
It was 100 percent good.
(It was 100 percent good.)
(A 100-point Ordinary Day)
(Next story)
(Exclaiming)
(The rookie at living alone, Gyeong Hye,)
(dove into independent life.)
(She's busily going to work today as well?)
(Peeking around)
(She's arrived at a construction site?)
(The cafe I used to work at closed down.)
(Seeing that by myself gave me mixed emotions.)
(Why am I choking up?)
(Hello.)
(It's a bummer.)
(She cheerfully says goodbye to the next door store owners.)
(Don't you need a part-timer here?)
(She looks for a job while she's at it.)
(I do need a part-timer!)
(Lively)
(What she's improved...)
(is her trying to do things by herself.)
(I'm the one who delved into the rough life.)
What do I do?
(I'm going to do everything that I want to do.)
(I'm missing a part.)
(Is it here?)
(Thump)
(Thud)
(Will you hold it for me, Wilson?)
(Sweating buckets)
(Fine. I can just shower four times.)
(I'm the Queen of Living Alone)
(Panting)
(Dae Ho is working out in the mountains?)
(Recently, I got a health checkup.)
(Dae Ho's health and daily routine have fallen apart lately.)
(To become healthier,)
(I wanted to make changes.)
Goodness.
(The first step toward a change)
(Cleaning the house)
(It's as clean as a new house.)
(Nana, you're happy that it's cleaner, right?)
(Drilling into the wall?)
(So he can work out as soon as he gets up,)
(he installs a home climbing wall.)
(It's what I want to do.)
(I can do anything to become healthy.)
(A fool who only cares about health)
(Taking a step toward...)
(healthier tomorrow)
(Let's go!)
(I feel healthy already.)
(Tomorrow, Dae Ho Will Be Healthy)